Finding Aid for Luedtke Engineering Company (Frankfort, Mich.) Organizational Records
Clarke Historical Library
Luedtke Engineering Company (Frankfort, Mich.) Organizational Records, 1932-2009
Luedtke Engineering Company (Frankfort, Mich.)
187 cubic ft. (in 375 boxes)
MSS.
The Organizational Records, 1932-2009, and undated, provide an unprecedented record of marine construction in the Great Lakes, including work on the Mackinac Bridge, the Soo Locks, and the Chicago Sanitary Canal, harbor work, dredging, and, more recent, habitat restoration projects.
Clarke Historical Library, Central Michigan University
Acc #75056
Luedtke Engineering Company (Frankfort, Mich.) Organizational Records are open for research. ALLERGY NOTE: Those with allergies should be aware that parts of the collection have a slight mildew odor. Researchers should exercise caution while using the collection.
Organizational History:
The Luedtke Engineering Company, a family-owned, Great Lakes-based marine engineering and construction company, was established on April 1st 1930, by Elroy “Duke” R. Luedtke. Located on Frankfort’s Betsy Bay, the company was set up in order to capitalize off of the Ann Arbor Railroad’s need for year round repair and construction services for their ferry operations. A family business, the original stock owners of Luedkte Engineering included Elroy Luedkte, Lucille Luedkte, and Fred Thacker.
Born in the town of Reedsville, Wisconsin in 1900, Elroy Luedkte graduated from the University of Wisconsin Engineering School in 1923. He went to work for the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, and then several private contractors before establishing his own business in 1930.
Elroy married his wife Lucille and had two sons, Karl and Erich, and one daughter, Gretchen. Mike Bauer became general superintendent after Elroy suffered a heart attack. Karl and Erich began working for their father’s company in 1955 and 1957 respectively.
Duke was a meticulous and detailed record keeper, a trait he passed onto his family and company.
On July 22, 1968 Elroy Luedkte died of a heart attack at his desk, passing, management of the company down to his sons. It was under the management of Karl and Erich Luedkte that the company saw the involvement of a third generation of Luedktes in the workforce.
Major events in the company’s history include:
1931 first steel sheet pile breakwater built in the world for Waukegan, Illinois, for the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers Chicago District.
1932 only job was rebuilding Algoma, Wisconsin, breakwater for U.S. Army Corps of Engineers.
1930s moving money to Marshall Ilsley bank before the national bank closure saved the company’s finances as the local banks where the company’s money had been did not reopen.
1933 dock work in Frankfort for Ann Arbor Railroad departing from their usual company.
1934 built Spectacle Reef and Minneapolis Shoal lighthouses. Company made profit 1932-1934.
1935 built breakwater at Kewaunee, Wisconsin, which allowed Company to buy first large crane.
1939-1942 placed stone on causeway for approach to what became Mackinaw Bridge on St. Ignace street.
1940 built water intake pipeline for Muskegon Heights.
1941-1945 during war years, the company’s net worth decline.
1941 built shipyard in Sturgeon Bay, Wisconsin.
1949 built 36 inch diameter water intake pipeline for Benton Harbor.
1950 company moved into market with private utilities when it built a subaqueous water intake at Sheboygan, Wisconsin, for Wisconsin Power and Light Company.
1950s period of steady growth.
1960s very profitable period. Major project was construction of two 14 foot diameter pipelines for Wisconsin, Michigan Power Company at Kewaunee, Wisconsin.
1970s very profitable period.
1971 moved into dredging business when dredged for Consumers Power Company, Pumped Storage Plant, Ludington.
1972 expanded, profitably, to Lake Erie. Mike Bauer retired.
1980s most profitable period in company. Karl Luedtke began having health issues.
1990s period of fluctuations in government and utilities cutbacks resulting in less work. Karl, his sons, Kurt, Paul and Alan, and Erich and his son, Chris, run business.
1994 Karl Luedtke died.
1996 Lucille Luedte died. Ownership passed to Kurt, Paul and Alan Luedtke. Chris Luedtke began his own business in Frankfort.
2000 the company’s 70th anniversary. (This information is from the collection.)
The collection is organized following its original order, by series, and within series by number, date, and format.
The Organizational Records, 1932-2009, and undated, provide an unprecedented record of marine construction in the Great Lakes, including work on the Mackinac Bridge, the Soo Locks, and the Chicago Sanitary Canal, harbor work, dredging, and, more recent, habitat restoration projects.
The records include the following four series: Professional Organizations and Local History, 1980-2009; Daily Reports, 1960-1993; Jobs, 1932-2002, and No Low Bids (NLBs), 1970-2002. In addition, one folder of organizational history materials, published and written notes, collected by the archivist, is found in the first folder in Box 1. The collection is organized following its original order, by series, and within series by number, date, and format.
Series1: Professional Organizations and Local History, 1980-2009 (3 boxes, 1.5 cubic ft.), includes records of the following organizations: AASD and MCC; BLU; DCA; NADC; and Benzie County Economic Development Corporation. The series documents the involvement of the Luedtke family in professional organizations and associations and in their local community. This series is organized alphabetical by organization name, type of format, and then chronologically.
AASD and MCC (the American Association of Small Dredging and Marine Construction Companies), which is the predecessor of the National Association of Dredging Contractors (NACD), Testimonial, Senate Committee on Small Business, September 21, 1987 (one folder in Box 1). This folder includes background information such as newspaper clippings, congressional testimony, witness lists.
Benzie County Economic Development Corporation, Annual Meeting Minutes, 1980-2009 (Box 2, .5 cubic foot) includes: agendas, meeting minutes, reports, board comments, bylaws, and attachments including guidelines to establish a port authority, consulting proposal, articles of incorporation, and as resignation letter.
BLUA (Betsie Lake Utilities Authority) organizational records, 2004-2008 (Box 3, .5 cubic foot), include: Articles of Incorporation, 1988; Correspondence, 2005; Engineering Proposal, 1998; photograph of board members, 2004; property purchases, 2004; meeting minutes, 2007-2008; and wastewater treatment facility improvements, 2003.
DCA (Dredging Contractors of America) Annual Meeting materials, 2001-2008 (part 6 folders in Box 1) includes: greetings, activities, maps, driving directions, lists of attendees, schedules of events, reception and banquet information, agendas, meeting Minutes, biographies of speakers, financial records, reports, and bylaws.
NADC (National Association of Dredging Contractors) Annual Meeting materials, 1988-1989 (3 folders in Box 1), includes: agendas, meeting minutes, reports, financial records, congressional reception materials, by-laws, and enclosures.
Series 2: Daily Reports, 1960-1993, Boxes 4-77 (73 boxes, 36.5 cubic feet). This series is on printed Daily Report forms. Each form includes the following information added in handwriting: job number, date, day, shift, location, names of men who worked that day, their classification and rate of pay, equipment used, hours worked, total figures. Daily Reports are organized by job number and begin with Job number 298, 1960. There are obvious skips in the sequential job numbers within the series which were present when the collection came to the Clarke.
Series 3: Jobs, 1932-2002, Boxes 77-314 (237 boxes, 118.5 cubic feet). This series includes the jobs that Luedtke bid on, won, and completed in Michigan and other states including Illinois, Wisconsin, New York, Indiana, Ohio, Minnesota, Pennsylvania, and California. Some of these jobs were for the U.S. Corps of Engineers, which was noted on the labels. Most of the jobs include building something in a marine environment, but Luedtke also hauled rocks, lifted sunken boats, and moved a crane. Each job may include some or all of the following material: communications (various types), bid opening form, bid proposal, contract, addendums to bid, bid proposal, and/or contract; drawings (various, often blue-lines), lists of cost, equipment, labor, hours; changes to contract, certificates or bills of insurance, quality assurance programs, claims, quality control, financials/cost sheets, permits, newspaper clippings (copies), contracts, orders for equipment, photographs, negatives, change orders, and survey reports. Some of the earliest photographs include 1920s photographs of Luedtke divers in hard hat suits for commercial diving (deep diving). There are also incident reports and notes about a fire in Chicago. The series is in order by job number, which is also in chronological order. The first Job documented is number 5, Waukegan, Illinois, 1932, and the last is Job 309, Kenosha, Wisconsin, 2002. The sequential job number is almost complete. Two jobs have no number and are filed in the order in which they were found: Job H, Mackinaw city, 1943 – 1944, and Job Unknown, Port Washington, WI, 1950.
Jobs of note include the following: Job 354 includes correspondence with Albert Kahn Associated Architects and Engineers, 1966. Job 692 includes vandalism and oil spill. Job 644 includes photographs of Luedtke on strike. Job 608 includes information that Luedtke was fined by the Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), see the correspondence on yellow paper. There are also several major lawsuits within this series, notably one with Chicago over a collapsed tunnel (Job 763), a long, vicious lawsuit in which Luedtke finally emerged vindicated.
Series 4: No Low Bids (NLBs), 1970-2002, Boxes 315-375 (60 boxes, 30 cubic feet) document jobs Luedtke either just collected data on and decided not to bid on, or jobs they collected data on, bid on, and lost to competitors. There are very few completed bids in this series. Some of these jobs were for the U.S. Coast Guard or the U.S. Corps of Engineers, which was noted on the labels. For each Michigan job the folder may include some of all of the following material: abstract, proposal and/or addendum, maps, photographs, negatives, bid form and instructions, description of work to be done, equipment to be used, survey reports, invitation to bid and addendums, drawings (various), communications (various), project manuals, Luedtke notes of informational meetings, and project planning notes (on green paper), and insurance bid bonds. Sometimes Luedtke sent letters protesting that the competitor who won the bid over Luedtke could not possibly do the job at the rate they promised. These letters have been retained in the series. Besides Michigan, there are NLBs for Wisconsin, Illinois, New York, Ohio, Michigan, Pennsylvania, Minnesota, Indiana, and Missouri. This series is in chronological by month, day and year. For labeling purposes, the name of the job and year was included on the folder label, not the month, but the strict chronological order in which they were originally filed was followed by the processors. This series was heavily weeded. Please refer to the processing notes for clarification on the weeding.
All the boxes in the collection are .5 cubic foot boxes, except for two, Box #4 and #351, which are both .25 cubic foot boxes, a point which is noted on the box and folder listing.
Allergy Note: Those with allergies should be aware that while the collection overall is in excellent condition, parts of it have a slight mildew odor. Researchers should exercise caution while using the collection.
Processing Note:
As per the donor agreement, all materials not retained by the Clarke were set aside to be reviewed by the donor. Materials weeded from the collection include duplicates, blank forms, taxes, miscellaneous financials and correspondence, and reading material. A total of 81 cubic feet (76 boxes) of material was withdrawn during processing.
The Jobs folder included lawsuit depositions which included social security numbers. Pages with social security numbers were removed or copied and the copies were retained. Much supporting documentation was withdrawn from the law suits. Lawsuit materials retained explain sufficiently what the lawsuit was, who was involved, and how it was finally settled. Also, all materials were retained for jobs at Detroit, Mackinaw and the Soo Locks.
The No Low Bid (NLB) series was heavily weeded. For out-of-state jobs that Luedtke actually bid on the Clarke retained the proposal, contract, addendums to both, and Luedtke notes (usually on green paper). Luedtke collected a lot of information in this series but did not always bid on the jobs. If there was no evidence that they actually bid on the job and it was out-of-state, the entire folder was weeded. If it was unclear if Luedtke bid on a job in Michigan, all the materials in the folder were retained and a note was put in from the archivist explaining the situation.
Subjects:
Kahn, Albert, 1869-1942.; Luedtke Engineering Company (Frankfort, Mich.); American Association of Small Dredging and Marine Construction Companies.; National Association of Dredging Contractors.; Benzie County Economic Development Corporation (Mich.); Betsie Lake Utilites Authority (Frankfort, Mich.); United States. Environmental Protection Agency.; Albert Kahn and Associated Architects and Engineers, Inc. (Detroit, Mich.); United States. Coast Guard.; United States. Army. Corps of Engineers.; Ann Arbor Railroad Company.; Specifications -- Engineering.; Public utilities.; Engineers -- Michigan.; Water withdrawals -- Illinois -- Chicago Sanitary and Ship Canal.; Deep diving -- United States -- History -- 20th century.; Deep diving -- Great Lakes (North America) -- History -- 20th century.; Great Lakes (North America) -- History -- Sources.; Great Lakes (North America) -- Commerce -- History.; Great Lakes (North America) -- Docks.; Great Lakes (North America) -- Dredging..; Great Lakes (North America) -- Harbors.; Great Lakes (North America) -- History -- 20th century.; Great Lakes (North America) -- Inland Water Transportation -- History -- 20th century.; Great Lakes (North America) -- Marinas.; Great Lakes (North America) -- Shipping -- History -- 20th century.; Great Lakes (North America) -- Salvage.; Michigan -- History -- Sources.; Frankfort (Mich.) -- History.; Soo Locks (Mich.) -- History.; Mackinac Bridge (Mich.) -- History.; Benzie County (Mich.) -- History.
- Luedtke Engineering Company (Frankfort, Mich.) Organizational Records.
  - Organizational Materials (copies),2015 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - AASD and MCC, Testimonial, Senate Committee on Small Business,September 21, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - DCA Annual Meeting,2001 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - DCA Annual Meeting,2004 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - DCA Annual Meeting,2005 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - DCA Annual Meeting,2006 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - DCA Annual Meeting,2007 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - DCA Annual Meeting,2008 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - NADC Annual Meeting,1988 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - NADC Annual Meeting,1989 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - NADC Background Information,1989 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Benzie County Economic Development Corporation, Annual Meeting Minutes,1980 – 1986 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Benzie County Economic Development Corporation, Annual Meeting Minutes,1987 – 1989 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Benzie County Economic Development Corporation, Annual Meeting Minutes,1995 – 1997 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Benzie County Economic Development Corporation, Annual Meeting Minutes,1998 – 2000 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Benzie County Economic Development Corporation, Annual Meeting Minutes,2001 – 2002 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Benzie County Economic Development Corporation, Annual Meeting Minutes,2003 – 2004 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Benzie County Economic Development Corporation, Annual Meeting Minutes,2005 – 2009 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - BLUA, Articles of Incorporation,April 12, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - BLUA, Correspondence,2005 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - BLUA, Engineering Proposal,June 11, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - BLUA, Photograph, 2004 Board Members,2004 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - BLUA, Property Purchases,2004 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - BLUA, Regular Meeting Minutes,2007 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - BLUA, Regular Meeting Minutes,January – July 2008 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - BLUA, Regular Meeting Minutes,August – December 2008 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - BLUA, Wastewater Treatment Facility Improvements, Basis of Design,April 28, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - (.25 cubic ft.): Daily Report, Job 38,1938 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - (.25 cubic ft.): Daily Report, Job 39,1939 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - (.25 cubic ft.): Daily Report, Job 50,1939 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - (.25 cubic ft.): Daily Report, Job 231,1952 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 298,1960 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 303,1960 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 305,1960 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 307,1961 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 307, 1960, 1 of 4,1960 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 307, 1960, 2 of 4,1960 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 307, 1960, 3 of 4,1960 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 307, 1960, 4 of 4,1960 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Daily Report, Job 307,1961 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Daily Report, Job 308, 1960, 1 of 2,1960 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Daily Report, Job 308, 1960, 2 of 2,1960 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Daily Report, Job 309,1960 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 310,1960 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 311, 1960, 1 of 3,1960 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 311, 1960, 2 of 3,1960 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 311, 1960, 3 of 3,1960 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 312,1960 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 313,1960 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 314,1960 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Daily Report, Job 315, 1961, 1 of 2,1961 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Daily Report, Job 315, 1961, 2 of 2,1961 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Daily Report, Job 316,1961 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Daily Report, Job 319, 1963, 1 of 2,1963 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Daily Report, Job 319, 1963, 2 of 2,1963 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 319,1964 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 320,1963 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 321,1963 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 322,1963 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 322,1964 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 323,1963 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 324,1963 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 325,1963 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Daily Report, Job 326, 1964, 1 of 2,1964 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Daily Report, Job 326, 1964, 2 of 2,1964 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Daily Report, Job 327,1963 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Daily Report, Job 328,1963 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Daily Report, Job 329,1964 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Daily Report, Job 330,1964 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Daily Report, Job 331,1964 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Daily Report, Job 332,1964 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Daily Report, Job 333,1964 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Daily Report, Job 334,1964 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 334,1965 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 335,1964 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 337, 1965, 1 of 2,1965 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 337, 1965, 2 of 2,1965 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 338,1964 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 339,1964 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 340,1964 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Daily Report, Job 340,1965 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Daily Report, Job 341,1965 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Daily Report, Job 342,1965 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Daily Report, Job 343,1965 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Daily Report, Job 345,1965 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Daily Report, Job 346,1965 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Daily Report, Job 347,1965 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 348,1965 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 349,1965 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 350,1965 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 454,1977 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 457, 1977, 1 of 9,1977 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 457, 1977, 2 of 9,1977 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 457, 1977, 3 of 9,1977 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Daily Report, Job 457, 1977, 4 of 9,1977 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 457, 1977, 5 of 9,1977 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 457, 1977, 6 of 9,1977 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 457, 1977, 7 of 9,1977 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 457, 1977, 8 of 9,1977 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 457, 1977, 9 of 9,1977 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 457,1978 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 460,1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 460, 1977, 1 of 4,1977 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 460, 1977, 2 of 4,1977 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 460, 1977, 3 of 4,1977 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 460, 1977, 4 of 4,1977 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 461,1977 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 462,1977 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 463,1977 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 464,1977 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 465, 1977, 1 of 3,1977 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 465, 1977, 2 of 3,1977 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 465, 1977, 3 of 3,1977 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 467,1977 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 469,1977 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Daily Report, Job 471, 1977, 1 of 3,1977 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Daily Report, Job 471, 1977, 2 of 3,1977 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Daily Report, Job 471, 1977, 3 of 3,1977 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 472,1977 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 473,1977 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 473, 1978, 1 of 2,1978 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 473, 1978, 2 of 2,1978 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 474,1977 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 474, 1978, 1 of 3,1978 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 474, 1978, 2 of 3,1978 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 474, 1978, 3 of 3,1978 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 475, 1978, 1 of 3,1978 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 475, 1978, 2 of 3,1978 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 475, 1978, 3 of 3,1978 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 475, 1979,1979 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 476,1977 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 477, 1 of 2,1977 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 477, 2 of 2,1977 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 477,1978 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 479,1977 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 480,1977 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 481,1977 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 481,1978 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Daily Report, Job 482,1978 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Daily Report, Job 483,1978 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Daily Report, Job 484,1978 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Daily Report, Job 485,1978 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Daily Report, Job 486,1978 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Daily Report, Job 487, 1978, 1 of 2,1978 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 487, 1978, 2 of 2,1978 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 487, 1979, 1 of 3,1979 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 487, 1979, 2 of 3,1979 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 487, 1979, 3 of 3,1979 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 488, 1978, 1 of 3,1978 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 488, 1978, 2 of 3,1978 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 488, 1978, 3 of 3,1978 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 489,1979 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 490, 1978, 1 of 3,1978 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 490, 1978, 2 of 3,1978 (Box 17, Folder 7)